portalseven.com 2016-11-24

# PortalSeven - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [contact@portalseven.com](mailto:contact@portalseven.com).

### Gathering and Use of Information

PortalSeven.com will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.portalseven.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.portalseven.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.portalseven.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.portalseven.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   
Google Adsense, YieldAds.com 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.portalseven.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.portalseven.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.portalseven.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### Acceptance of these PortalSeven.com Web Site Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this PortalSeven.com Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

From time to time, PortalSeven.com may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the PortalSeven.com Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [contact@portalseven.com](mailto:contact@portalseven.com).

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies [Click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
